previously on Desperate Housewives
上集回顾...
i'm granng you temporary custody
我授予你们暂时监管权
until we can get a straight answer from e birth father.
直到我们从她生父那里得到直接回答
Gabrielle got exactly what she wanted.
Gabrielle得到了她想要的
if edie doesn't know,
既然edie不知情
then that means that you just cheated on her with me.
也就是说 你欺骗了她 还有我
susan got fooled again...
susan再次被愚弄...
i'm also a member of s.a.
我同时还是SA的一名会员
and bree got too much...
而bree 则知道的...
sex addicts anonymous.
就是禁欲协会
information.
太多
karl mayer didn't pray often, but when he did,
karl mayer不常祈祷 但一旦他祈祷了
it was usually to ask for god's help
那通常是为了祈求上帝保佑他
in breaking up with a woman
能顺利地甩掉一个女人
and to spare him the nasty drama
并且帮他省掉 那些电视情节
that usually accompanied
那些伴随着分手的
such callous and unexpected departures.
冷酷而又突然的离别
over the years, karl had dumped dozens of women,
这些年来 karl甩掉了很多女人
and not one of them had ever seen it coming.
但没有一个是面对面的
every retreat was always meticulously planned,
他的每一次鸣金收兵 都在事先进行了周密的计划
right down to the personalized stationary,
都采用了亲笔信的形式
hence his record of successful getaways
这也是他可以一次次甩掉女人
from women who did not want to see him go.
同时还能避免尴尬的秘诀所在
so when he decided to break up with edie britt,
所以当他决定同edie britt分手的时候
karl prayed to god yet again to help him avoid
karl再次祈祷上帝 帮助他省略掉
all the unnecessary drama.
所有那些不必要的电视情节
unfortunately for karl...
但不幸的是...
GOD WAS IN THE MOOD...
上帝正想着...
TO BE ENTERTAINED.
找点乐子
COME ON!
快啊
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- 这到底是怎么回事？
EDIE,BABY,CA DOWN.
Edie，亲爱的，冷静一点
"LET'S BE HONEST WITH OURSELVES,EDIE.
我们还是面对现实吧
WE HAVEN'T BEEN HAPPY IN A LONG TIME"?
“Edie，我们在一起你一直不开心？”
WHO ARE YOU TO TELL ME I HAVEN'T BEEN HAPPY,
你是谁啊？要你来跟我说我不开心
YOU MISERABLE SON OF A BITCH? I HAVE BEEN ECSTATIC!
你这可悲的混蛋！ 我一直很开心！
OKAY. I-I'M THE ONE WHO HASN'T BEEN HAPPY,THEN.
好的 是我不开心
THEY WHY DID YOU PROPOSE TO ME?
- 那你为什么向我求婚？
I DON'T KNOW.
我也不知道
I HAVE TOLD EVERY WOMAN IN THIS TOWN
我已经跟镇上每个姐妹说了
THAT WE ARE GETTING MARRIED, AND ALL YOU HAVE TO SAY TO ME
说了我们要结婚了 而你现在却对我说
IS,"I DON'T KNOW"?
- 对我说“我不知道”？
OH,WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
你还要我说什么？
I'M SORRY.
对不起
WHAT'S GOING ON? IS THERE SOMEONE ELSE?
发生了什么？ 是不是你有了别人？
OH,MY GOD.
噢，我的上帝啊！
OH,CRAP.
噢，糟糕！
COME ON,COME ON,COME ON!
快点，快点！
AS HE SAT THERE, KARL COULDN'T HELP BUT WONDER
坐在车里，Karl不禁想问
WHY GOD HAD FORSAKEN HIM.
为什么上帝要抛弃他
IT NEVER OCCURRED TO HIM THAT GOD...
他从来没想到过 上帝...
MIGHT BE A WOMAN.
可能是女人
The Desperate Housewives Season 02  Episode 20 IT WASN'T TO HAPPEN
绝望的主妇 第2季 第20集 本不应该发生 校对 时间轴: 灰狼爱白兔
GOD, GRANT ME THE SERENITY
上帝啊 请赐予我安详
TO ACCEPT THE THINGS I CANNOT CHANGE,
让我们接受不能改变的东西
THE COURAGE TO CHANGE THE THINGS I CAN
让我们拥有改变能够改变的东西的勇气
AND THE WISDOM TO KNOW THE DIFFERENCE...
赐予我辨别事实的睿智...
THE MEMBERS OF THE FAIRVIEW CHAPTER OF A.A.
Fairview的嗜酒者互助协会的成员
ENDED EVERY MEETING WITH A PRAYER.
在每次聚会的最后都要祈祷
AND WHILE MOST WERE ASKING GOD FOR HELP
他们大部分都会祈求上帝帮自己
IN RESISTING TEMPTATION,
抵御诱惑
WAS BUSY THINKING THOUGHTS THAT WERE DOWNRIGHT SINFUL.
而Bree却想着一些罪孽的事情
...WITH HIM IN THE NEXT. AMEN.
...来世依然和神在一起 阿门
KEEP COMING BACK. IT WORKS IF YOU WORK IT.
请帮助我们吧 只要有你帮助，一定能够成功
AMEN.
阿门
I THINK YOU'D LOVE THE OPERA.
我想你喜欢那出歌剧
THE MUSIC AND THE VOICES- IT'S JUST ALL SO... PASSIONATE.
音乐和唱腔都那么有激情
YEAH,A 300-POUND SOPRANO SEDUCING BALDING TENORS.
是的，300磅重的女高音 在引诱一群秃顶的男高音
THAT'D BE HOT.
- 那棒极了
YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
你在取笑我？
HUH?
嗯？
BREE.
Bree
YES?
怎么？
MAYBE A LITTLE BIT.
可能有一点
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
你们在干嘛？
CLAUDE?
Claude？
WE MADE PLANS,REMEMBER?
我们说好的，记得吗？
I'M SORRY. I WAS JUST ABOUT-
对不起，我只是要-
YEAH,I SAW WHAT YOU WERE JUST ABOUT TO DO.
嗯，我看见你要做什么了
I'M SORRY,PETER, BUT,UH,WHO IS THIS?
对不起，Peter 嗯，这是谁？
THIS IS CLAUDE. HE'S MY SPONSOR.
这是Claude，我的互助伙伴
OH,YOUR A.A. SPONSOR?
你在嗜酒者互助会的伙伴？
NO. I'M HIS OTHER SPONSOR.
不，别的协会的伙伴
FOR MY SEX ADDICTION.
诫性瘾的协会
DAMN IT,PETER. WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
妈的，Peter，我跟你说过什么？
AVOID LUST TRIGGERS.
避免诱惑的诱因
AND WHAT IS SHE?
那她是什么？
COME ON, DON'T DO THIS,MAN.
拜托，别这样，伙计
SHE'S A LUST TRIGGER. A LUST TRIGGER!
她是诱惑的诱因 诱惑诱因！
UM,EXCUSE ME. I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
嗯，对不起 我不知道那词是什么意思
BUT COULD YOU PLEASE STOP SAYING IT?
但是麻烦你别在说那词了，好吗？
WHERE'S YOUR CHIP? GIVE IT TO ME.
你的筹码呢？ 给我
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW LOW YOU'D SUNK WHEN WE MET?
你还记得我们认识时你有多糟糕吗？
THIS REPRESENTS 12 MONTHS OF HARD WORK,
这代表12个月的艰苦努力
NOT GIVING IN TO YOUR URGES.
别向欲望屈服
NOW IF YOU WANNA BLOW ALL THAT ON THIS WOMAN,
如果你要为这女人放弃这一切
JUST TELL ME NOW SO I CAN STOP WASTING MY TIME
那现在就告诉我 免得我浪费时间
WORKING WITH YOU.
在你身上
I DON'T WANT TO BLOW IT.
我不想放弃
GOOD.
很好
TH TELL THE PRETTY LADY GOOD-BYE
那就和这美丽的女士说再见吧
AND THAT YOU CAN'T SOCIALIZE WITH HER ANYMORE.
你以后再也不能和她交往
AND DO IT QUICK.
快点行事
I'M HUNGRY.
我饿了
BAD NEWS.
坏消息
ED WANTS US TO PUSH THROUGH TONIGHT
Ed要我们熬夜赶工
AND FINISH THE EDELSTEIN REALTY PITCH.
把Edelstein地产的项目做完
BUT WE'RE NOT PRESENTING FOR ANOTHER TWO WEEKS.
但是要过两周才做展示
WHY DON'T WE START TOMORROW?
明天再做不行吗？
BUT HOW WOULD THAT HELP ED AVOID HIS MARITAL PROBLEMS?
- 这怎么能帮Ed解决他的婚姻问题呢？
WHAT?
什么？
OH,HE'S RIGHT. I HEAR ED FIGHTING WITH FRAN ON THE PHONE
噢，他说得对 我听见Ed和Fran在电话里吵架
EVERY DAY THROUGH THE OFFICE WALLS.
- 每天都听到
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN ALL OUR WORKING HOURS.
这就是我们老是加班的原因
AH,BUT YOU LUCKED OUT,SCAVO. DARLENE TALKED HIM INTO CUTTING
嗯，但你没事，Scavo Darlene跟他说
THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE KIDS IN DAY CARE LOOSE.
那些白天照看小孩的人可以回家
HEY,GREAT. LET'S GO BEFORE HE CHANGES HIS MIND.
嘿，很好 我们快走，免得他改变主意
BUT THAT DSN'T INCLUDE YOU, MISS SENIOR V.P.
但你例外，副总裁女士
ED WANTS YOU IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM NOW.
- Ed要你现在就去会议室
YOU'RE KIDDING!
开玩笑吧！
YOU'RE HIS SECURITY BLANKET, LYNETTE. HE STAYS,YOU STAY.
你是他的保险毯，Lynette 他不走，你也不能走
JERRY,CAN YOU HELP ME GET THE KIDS DOWN TO THE CAR?
Jerry，麻烦你帮我把孩子们送上车
OH. YEAH.
好的
THANKS,JER.
- 谢谢，Jer
SURE.
不谢
LYNETTE?
- Lynette？
YEAH?
什么事？
GET THOSE MOCK-UPS TOGETHER, WILL YOU?
把那些版面整理好，好吗？
JERRY,I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A KID.
Jerry，我怎么不知道你有小孩？
Y- YEAH,UM,OUT OF WEDLOCK.
是的，嗯，非婚生的
SO... SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
那么，明天见
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
对不起我迟到了
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- 怎么了？
KARL BROKE UP WITH EDIE.
Karl和Edie分手了
OH,MY GOD.
噢，天啊！
YEAH,APPARENTLY, HE WAS SEEING SOMEONE.
是的，很明显，他有了别人
REALLY?
是吗？
DID HE SAY WHO IT WAS?
他说是谁了吗？
I KNOW WHO SHE IS.
我知道是谁
SHE'S A MAN-EATING, SCUM-SUCKING HO-BAG.
她是个吃人的喜欢口交的婊子
NO,HE DID NOT SAY.
不，他没说
YOU KNOW, WHEN KARL DUMPED YOU,
Karl甩掉你的时候
I THOUGHT THAT IT WAS ALL YOUR FAULT.
我以为全是你的错
YEAH,I FIGURED THAT... YOU WERE A NAG OR BAD IN BED.
是的，我以前只知道知道... 你床上功夫不行
BUT NOW I... NOW I SEE THAT YOU WERE JUST A VICTIM,TOO.
但我现在知道你也是个牺牲品
WE HAVE A BOND,SUSAN.
咱俩同病相怜，Susan
IT'S LIKE WE'RE SISTERS.
我们就像姐妹一样
THERE'S EVEN A PRETTY ONE AND AN UGLY ONE.
一个漂亮一个难看
EDIE!
Edie！
NO,I'M JUST SAYING THAT KARL SCREWED US BOTH.
我只是说Karl把我们俩都毁了
YES,LIKE YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
是的，难以置信
GUYS,I'M ALL FOR BASHING EXES, BUT LET'S SAVE
伙伴们，我支持诋毁前人男友 但我们还是
A LITTLE OF OUR HATE FOR HIS PARTNER IN CRIME-
还是留点给他的同伙-
THE OTHER WOMAN.
- 那个女人
MM-HMM.
对
YEAH! YOU KNOW,THEY'RE ALWAYS COMING UP WITH THESE EXCUSES
是的！他们总是有借口
TO JUSTIFY BEING A HOME-WRECKER.
来为他们毁掉他人家庭辩解
EXACTLY! LIKE, "HE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN WITH ME
就是！就像“他不会和我在一起
IF HE WAS GETTIN' IT AT HOME."
如果他在家能得到满足的话”
YEAH,"HONEY, YOU'RE THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
就是，“亲爱的，你才是我一生所爱
SHE'S JUST THE RUNNER-UP."
她只是后备轮胎”
OH,LOOK,THE BABY'S DOING SOMETHING REALLY CUTE.
噢，看，孩子在吸什么东西
SHE'S SLEEPING.
她在睡觉
LIKE AN ANGEL.
像天使一样
LOOK,I THINK WE ALL KNOW THAT KARL IS A DOG. MM.
我们都知道Karl是个混蛋
I MEAN,BUT LET'S FACE IT- IF THESE TRAMPS
我是说，不光是Karl的问题
WEREN'T LAYING OUT THE BUFFET, HE WOULDN'T BE CHOWING DOWN.
一个巴掌拍不响
WELL,EVERY SITUATION DIFFERENT,
嗯，每个情况都不同
AND IT'S HARD TO JUDGE UNTIL WE KNOW ALL THE DETAILS.
在我们知道细节之前，很难作出判断
WHICH...
而这...
OBVIOUSLY I DON'T KNOW, BECAUSE HOW WOULD I KNOW?
很明显我也不知道 我怎么会知道呢？
SHE'S A SLUTTY,SLUTTY WHORE. ABSOLUTELY.
她是个放荡的婊子 肯定是
YEAH.
是的
ARE YOU SURE SHE NEEDS THAT? I JUST PUT SUNSCREEN ON HER.
还需要穿这个吗？ 我刚刚给她擦了防晒霜了
YES,SHE NEEDS THE BONNET. ITOMPLETES THE OUTFIT.
恩，要带这帽子 是一套的
OH,FOR GOD'S SAKES,GABY.
Gaby，看在上帝的份上
SHE'S NEVER TOO YOUNG TO START ACCESSORIZING.
虽然她还小，但开始打扮也不为早
BESIDES,ALL THE NEIGHBORS ARE OUT TODAY,
而且，今天所有的邻居们都在
AND I WANT THEM TO SEE HOW HAPPY WE ARE AND WISH THEY WERE US.
我要他们看看我们多么快乐 让他们羡慕我们
HEY.
嘿
UH,THE BABY'S A BEAUTY.
嗯，小孩很漂亮
WE THINK SO, BUT WE'RE A LITTLE BIASED.
是的 但是我们有点偏见
OH,WOW, SHE'S GOT MY EYES.
噢，她的眼睛跟我的一模一样
HUH?
嗯？
OH,I'M DALE.
噢，我是Dale
DALE HELM. I'M THE BABY'S BIRTH FATHER.
Dale Helm，我是孩子的生父
UH,WELL,HI,DALE.
嗯，你好，Dale
NICE TO MEET YOU.
很高兴见到你
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
很多人在找你
YEAH,I KNOW, LAWYERS AND STUFF.
是的，我知道 律师还有法庭的人
I GOT KINDA HELD UP IN FLORIDA LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
我在佛罗里达有点事，耽误了一段时间
SPRING BREAK,RIGHT?
春季假期，对吧？
YEAH. OH,MAN, WE WERE WASTED 24/7.
是的，伙计 我们整天都无事可做
THEN I GOT THE MESSAGE AND JUST THOUGHT
然后就收到短信
MY FRIENDS WERE MESSING WITH ME. THOSE BUTTWADS!
以为是我的朋友在捉弄我 那些酒鬼！
WELL,IT'S A GOOD THING HE'S HERE.
嗯，他在这里是好事
WE CAN TAKE HIM TO THE LAWYER'S OFFICE,
我们可以带他去律师的办公室
AND YOU CAN SIGN OVER FULL CUSTODY TO US.
你可以把监护权完全转移给我们
OKAY.
好的
YEAH,UH, THE THING ABOUT THAT IS,
嗯，关于这事情
I'M GONNA WANT THE BABY.
我要这个孩子
COME ON,YOU GUYS. WE DON'T HAVE TO MAKE THIS UGLY.
拜托，两位 我们没必要把这事情弄得很难看
YOU'RE TRYING TAKE OUR BABY! HOW IS IT NOT GONNA BE UGLY?
你想带走我们的孩子 怎么会不难看
JUST KEEP WALKING,GABY. DON'T ENGAGE HIM.
继续走，别理他
LISTEN,MR. SOLIS...
听着，Solis先生...
NO,YOU LISTEN! WE WERE GRANTED CUSTODY.
不，你听着 我们是监护人
IF YOU WANT HER, YOU TALK TO THE JUDGE.
想得到她，跟法官讲吧
HEY,WHAT IS THE HOLDUP?
- 怎么这么慢？
THEY TOLD ME I GOTTA TALK TO A JUDGE.
他们让我找法官
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING HERE, FRANK?
你在这干什么，Frank?
IT'S HIS BABY. GIVE IT TO HIM!
是他的孩子，给他
LIKE HELL!
- 见鬼去!
HEY,MRS. SOLIS,CAN I SEE THE BABY?
我能看看孩子么？
NO!
- 不行！
DALE,JUST DO IT ALREADY!
Dale，直接动手
I'M NOT JUST GONNA KIDNAP IT.
- 我不能绑架
WHY NOT? THEY DID!
干吗不？他们就是绑架
IT IS YOUR BABY. JUST TAKE IT!
这是你的孩子，动手吧
TRY IT.
试试看
FRANK?
Frank?
GET IN,YOU MORON.
上车，笨蛋
ANYWAYS,IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE DOING A GOOD JOB WITH HER.
不过你们好象对她不错
DUMB-ASS!
笨驴!
SHE SEEMS CLEAN.
她好干净
AND LIKE I SAID, WE HAVE BEEN VERY HAPPY HERE,
正如我说的 我们住得很高兴
AND I'M SURE YOU WILL BE,TOO.
你们也会的
WELL,WE JUST LOVE IT. YEAH.
我们很喜欢 是的
ONCE THE STAIRS ARE REPAIRED, I'LL SHOW YOU THE BASEMENT.
楼梯修好后 我带你们看地下室
WHAT'S GOING ON?
怎么回事？
THE HOUSE JUST SOLD.
房子刚卖了
START PACKING.
开始搬家
WHY DON'T YOU JUST PUT CALEB IN AN INSTITUTION?
为什么不把Caleb交给收容所
IT'S WHERE HE BELONGS ANYWAY.
- 他早晚要去
MY MOM WOULD NEVER LET STRANGERS TAKE CARE OF HIM.
我妈不让陌生人照顾他
THEN WHY DON'T YOU CALL THE POLICE?
为什么不报警？
THEN IT'S NOT UP TO HER.
- 那样就不由她了
IF I CALL THE POLICE,
如果我报警
MY MOM AND I GO TO JAIL WITH CALEB.
我，妈，Caleb都要进监狱
WE'VE BEEN HIDING A MURDERER. NOW,LOOK,IF WE-
我们窝藏杀人犯 你瞧，如果我们...
IF WE DO MOVE,I PROMISE I WILL CALL YOU EVERY DAY.
如果我们搬走了 我保证每天给你打电话
I DON'T NEED A PHONE BUDDY. I NEED A BOYFRIEND!
我不要聊友 我要一个男朋友
WOULD YOU CALM DOWN,PLEASE?
- 冷静下来好么？
DON'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO!
不要指手画脚
YOU KNOW,I COULD GO TO THE POLICE MYSELF!
我可以自己去报警
DANIELLE...
- Danielle...
I JUST...I LOVE YOU SO CH.
我只是...太爱你了
I WOULD DO ANYTHING TO KEEP YOU HERE.
我会尽全力留住你
YEAH,I SEE THAT NOW.
是，我看到了
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME ALONE HERE. YOU HAVE TO THINK OF SOMETHING.
你不能把我留在这 想想办法
DON'T WORRY.
别担心
I WILL.
我会的
When r u coming home?
何时回家？
At this rate?never
这种效率？别想
He's keeping you late and i'm horny!
你要加班，而我很饥渴！
What do u want me 2 do about that?
你要我怎样？
Dunno.what do u want 2 do?
不知道，你想怎样
making coffee...u want?
你要冲咖啡？
I want to lick u from head to foot
我想舔遍你全身
OH,MY GOD!
哦，天哪！
ED? HEY,I'M SO SORRY,
对不起
BUT OBVIOUSLY THAT WAS JUST MEANT FOR TOM'S EYES ONLY.
那显然只是说给Tom的
HONEST MISTAKE. DON'T EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
无心之过
OKAY.
OK
THANKS. WELL,I'M GONNA GO BACK IN MY OFFICE
谢谢，我回办公室去了
AND CONTINUE TO FEEL LIKE A HUGE PERVERT.
继续感觉像个性变态
AT LEAST YOU AND TOM HAVE A LOVE LIFE.
至少你和Tom有感情生活
WELL,WE DO THE BEST WE CAN GIVEN THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
我们都尽力 环境允许的话
BETTER THAN FRAN AND I. WE'RE DEAD IN THAT DEPARTMENT.
比我和Fran好 我们像死在公寓里
I DON'T WANNA BORE YOU WITH THE DETAILS.
我不想拿细节再烦你
I APPRECIATE THAT.
心领了
YOU KNOW,ED...
你知道么，Ed...
I DON'T WANNA PRY INTO YOUR PERSONAL BUSINESS,
我不想多管闲事，但...
BUT IF YOU ARE HAVING PROBLEMS IN THAT AREA,
如果你在这方面有问题
YOU DON'T HAVE TOE RESIGNED TO IT.
你不必听天由命
WHAT ARE YOU SUGGESTING, HOOKERS?
你建议什么 招妓？
NO,ED FERRARA DOESN'T PAY FOR SEX.
不，本人不为性花钱
I MEAN,YOU AND FRAN COULD SPICE IT UP A BIT.
我是说 你和Fran可以调调情
YOU KNOW,GET THE OLD JUICES FLOWING AGAIN.
重温旧梦
OH,I SEE.
知道了
KINDA LIKE,UH...
比如...
"I'D LIKE TO LICK YOU FROM HEAD TO FOOT."
"我想舔遍你全身"
OKAY,WELL, THAT WASN'T MY BEST WORK,
那不是最拿手的
BUT YOU CAN'T DENY RESULTS.
但效果不可小视
I.M.ing WORKS, AND WHEN I GO HOME TONHT,
“我要...”非常管用 今晚回去后
TOM AND I ARE GOING TO...
Tom和我会...
OKAY,WELL, I'M GONNA BE EXHAUSTED,
好吧，我累坏了
SO I'LL PROBABLY JUST LAY THERE. BUT TRUST,
大概只是躺着 但相信我
TOM IS GONNA GO TO TOWN.
Tom会奉陪到底go to town
IT'S SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT, LORD KNOWS.
可以考虑，谁知道呢
YOU KNOW WHAT THE SAD TRUTH IS?
不幸的是...
I HAVE BEEN THINKING ABOUT HOOKERS.
我已经在考虑招妓了
OKAY!
OK
UH,WELL, I HOPE THAT HELPED.
我希望那有用
AND I'M JUST GONNA GO BACK AND FINISH
我要回去完成工作
SO WE CAN ALL GET OUT OF HERE.
然后大家各奔东西
LET ME GUESS. YOU'RE NOT HERE FOR A BEAR CLAW.
让我猜猜 你不是来买熊仔饼
NO,I'M NOT.
不是
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
你在浪费时间
LOOK,YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT PETER,
你不必为Peter担心
NOT WHILE HE'S WITH ME.
起码和我在一起时
YEAH? WHY IS THAT?
是么？为什么？
BECAUSE WHEN IT COMES TO SEX,
因为当发展到性时
I HAVE AN UNWAVERING MORAL COMPASS.
我有坚定的道德界限
TRULY. A MAN COULD BEG AND PLEAD ALL DAY LONG,
真的，一个男人整日哀求
AND IT WOULDN'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE.
我也不为所动
SO SINCE I HAVE SUCH STRONG SELF-CONTROL,
我有如此强的自控力
THERE'S REALLY NO REASON FOR US TO END OUR FRIENDSHIP.
没有理由结束我们的友谊
THE GUY'S A TICKINBOMB.
这家伙是定时炸弹
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
你不了解
THE KIND OF DEPRAVITY THAT COMES WITH THIS DISEASE.
这种病带来的堕落
WAKING UP IN A STRANGER'S BED EVERY MORNING...
每天在陌生人的床上醒来...
CRUISING THE PARK AT NIGHT,
整晚在公园游荡
LOOKING FOR SOMEBODY TO GET OFF WITH,
找人亲热
COMPULSIVE MASTURBATION EVERY CHANCE YOU GET!
在任何可能的机会手淫
LOOK,FOR GUYS LIKE PETER AND ME,
像Peter和我这样的人
THERE'S NO BEAUTY IN THE SEX.
性没有美好的一面
IT'S AN EMPTY AND UGLY COMPULSION.
只是空洞丑陋的冲动
WELL,I AM SORRY,
对不起
BUT THE PETER I KNOW HAS A LITTLE MORE S-
我知道的Peter还...
HOLD UP.
等等
CLAUDE,I NEED SOME- I NEED SOME HELP.
Claude，我需要帮助
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? ARE YOU USING?
你来这干嘛？ 又磕药了？
NO,BUT I BOUGHT A BAG.
没，但我买了一袋
YOU'RE AN EMBARRASSMENTO ME. GIVE.
你让我丢脸，拿来
THERE'S A MEETING OVER ON 10th STREET. YOU GO THERE.
第10大街有个集会，你到那去
YOU CALL ME AFTER.
之后打电话
I'M SORRY.
对不起
GET THE HELL OUT OF MY SHOP.
滚出去
I'M ALSO A SPONSOR AT COCAINE ANONYMOUS.
我还是可卡因互助协会一员
WELL,AREN'T YOU THE RENAISSANCE MAN.
你真是多才多艺
ARE WE DONE HERE, PRINCESS?
说完了么，公主？
NOT YET. YOU OBVIOUSLY HAVE AN ENCYCLOPEDIC GRASP OF EVERYTHING DEAVED.
还没，你显然对一切 堕落的东西都融会贯通
BUT CLEARLY,YOU DON'T HAVE THE SLIGHTEST IDEA
但你没有一丁点
ABOUT THE POWER OF A LOVING RELATIONSHIP.
关于爱情力量的概念
THIS IS ALL YOU ARE TO PETER-
你对Peter来说就是这个
SOMETHING TO SATISFY HIS ADDICTION.
让他过瘾
WELL,I THINK PETER IS A BETTER MAN THAN YOU DO,
我认为Peter比你想象的好
AND I AM NOT GONNA LET YOU KEEP US APART.
- 我不会让你把我们分开
TRY AND STOP ME.
试试看
PETER DOES EVERYTHING I TELL HIM TO DO.
Peter完全听我的
THAT'S THE ONE THING YOU CAN DEPEND ON WITH ADDICTS-
成瘾者有一点可以利用
THEY'RE WEAK.
他们软弱
EXCUSE ME.
对不起
MAY I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
可以问些事情么？
YES,MA'AM?
请讲
IF A CITIZEN, AN ORDINARY CITIZEN LIKE MYSELF,
如果一个市民 像我一样的普通市民
KNEW OF SOMEONE HOLDING A SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF DRUGS,
知道某人藏有大量毒品
WHAT WOULD MY RESPONSIBILITIES BE,
我的义务是什么？
YOU KNOW,UNDER THE LAW?
在法律规定下
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
这是干什么?
AND THIS ONE, I RAN OUT AND GOT
我跑去买了这个
THE DAY I FOUND OUT KARL WAS DOING IT WITH HIS SEETARY.
当我发现KarL和秘书搞在一起
I THINK YOU'LL FIND THIS PARTICULARLY HELPFUL.
你会发现这很有帮助
IT'S GOT A CHAPTER CALLED,
有一章叫做
YOU'RE ONLY HURTING YOURSELF." YEAH,YOU KNOW,
“复仇只会伤害自己”
I'M JUST REALLY NOT INTO THE WHOLE READING THING.
我现在不想读书
OH. WELL,UM,WHY DON'T WE GET YOU OUT OF HERE?
为什么不出去
LET'S GO SEE A FEEL-GOOD MOVIE.
去看电影散心
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO NICE TO ME?
你为什么对我这么好？
WELL,I JUST WANNA HELP. SO HOW ABOUT THAT MOVIE?
我只想帮忙 看电影怎样？
YOU KNOW HOW I LIKE TO HEAL?
你知道我想怎样恢复？
I GET HAMMERED.
大醉一场
UH... WELL,UM...
那好...
THEN I SHOULD JUST GO AND LET YOU GET STARTED WITH THAT.
我离开然后你开始
DO YOU REALLY WANNA HELP ME? GOOD.
你真想帮我？很好
'CAUSE I'M GONNA NEED A DESIGNATED DRIVER.
因为我需要专门的司机
OKAY.
OK
HOW COULD HE BE ARRESTED FOR COCAINE POSSESSION?
他怎会因持有毒品被捕？
CLAUDE SWORE HE WAS CLEAN.
Claude发誓戒掉了
IT'S JUST AWFUL,ISN'T IT?
太糟糕了不是么？
I MEAN,YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT PEOPLE ARE DOING BEHIND YOUR BACK.
我是说，你永远不知道 人们背地里在做什么
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME MILK WITH YOUR COOKIES?
要牛奶配甜点么？
THANKS.
谢谢
IT'S JUST,YOU KNOW...
只是，你知道...
WAS HE BEST SPONSOR I'VE EVER HAD,
他是最好的互助伙伴
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO NOW.
我不知道现在该怎么办
WELL,I HAVE BEEN DOING SOME THINKING AND...
我想了一下...
HERE'S A THOUGHT- WHY DON'T I BE YOUR SPONSOR?
是这样... 我作你的互助伙伴
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
别开玩笑
YOU DON'T KNOW SQUAT ABOUT SEX ADDICTION.
你对性成瘾丝毫不懂
WELL,CRAVINGS ARE CRAVINGS,
渴望归渴望
AND ALL YOU REALLY NEED IS A FRIEND TO CALL
你需要的只是一个朋友
WHEN YOU START HAVING INAPPROPRIATE THOUGHTS,
当有不当想法时可以求助
AND I CAN BE THAT FRIEND.
我可以做这个朋友
WELL,THERE'S MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
还有很多
CLAUDE RESCUED ME FROM SOME PRETTY NASTY SCES OVER THE YEARS.
Claude多次把我从 十分难堪的场面中救出来
WELL,IF YOU WERE IN TROUBLE, I COULD HANDLE IT.
如果你有麻烦，我可以搞定
HOW CAN YOU BE SO SURE?
你怎能如此肯定
BECAUSE I CAN BE VERY STRONG
因为我会非常坚强
FOR THOSE PEOPLE THAT I REALLY CARE AUT.
为了真正关心的人
HOW CAN YOU HAVE ANY FEELINGS FOR ME AT ALL?
你怎会对我有感觉？
I MEAN,YOU'VE ONLY KNOWN ME FOR A FEW WEEKS.
我是说，我们只认识了几星期
YES,AND IN THAT TIME,
是啊，在这段时间里
I'VE COME TO LEARN THAT YOU'RE GOOD AND KIND AND SMART.
我发现你人品好，聪明
AND,YES, YOU HAVE A LITTLE PROBLEM
是有一点小问题
THAT YOU NEED SOME HELP WITH,
需要帮助
BUT I'M WILLING TO BE THERE FOR YOU.
但我愿意挺身而出
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
没什么大不了的
IF YOU SAW ME AT MY WORST,
如果你见到我最糟糕的时候
YOU MIGHT NOT LIKE ME SO MUCH.
就不那么喜欢我了
PETER, LET ME BE YOUR ROCK.
Peter，让我支持你
TAKING CARE OF PEOPLE IS WHAT I DO BEST.
照顾别人是我最拿手的
DRINK YOUR MILK.
喝牛奶
I ASKED FOR EXTRA SPICY.
我要的是重辣
I'M PRETTY SURE YOU SAID MEDIUM.
我很肯定你刚才说的是中辣
ARE YOU? WELL, MAYBE IF YOU'D WRITTEN IT DOWN,
你肯定？ 要是你刚才记下来的话
YOU WOULD'VE SPARED YOURSELF
现在就不用
THE WALK OF SHAME BACK TO THE KITCHEN.
丢脸地拿着东西走回厨房了
EDIE,WHY ARE YOU TORTURING THAT GIRL?
Edie，你干嘛折腾那女孩？
THAT IS HER. THAT IS THE ONE THAT KARL IS IN LOVE WITH.
就是她，Karl就是爱上她了
WE HAVE BEEN HERE A MILLION TIMES,
我们以前来过无数次了
AND YOU SHOULD SEE THE WAY THAT SHE FLIRTS WITH HIM,
你真该看看她是怎么和他卖弄风骚的
AND WHEN SHE COMES BACK HERE, I AM GONNA SHOVE THIS PITCHER
等她回来我要教训她
IN HER PERKY LITTLE MUG, AND WHEN SHE'S-
拿酒泼她，然后等她...
OKAY,LET'S NOT MAKE A SCENE. IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
好了，不要找麻烦，不值得
FOR THE SAKE OF ARGUMENT,
为了别吵起来
LET'S-LET'S-LET'S SAY THAT IT'S SOMEONE ELSE.
我们，我们就当是别人吧
YOU KNOW,PROBABLY IT WOULD BE A VULNERABLE,LONELY WOMAN
可能，可能是个孤独无助的女人
WHO KARL JUST TOOK ADVANTAGE OF,
恰好被Karl占了便宜
AND WHAT IF...
而且要是...
THIS POOR,CONFUSED SOUL BEGGED YOUR FORGIVENESS?
要是这个可怜，不知所措的女人 求你原谅呢？
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY?
你会怎样？
I'D SAY...
我会说...
"TOO LITTLE, TOO LATE,BITCH,"
“太假了，太迟了，贱人”
AND THEN I'D KICK HER.
然后，我就给她点颜色看看
YEAH,BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT,
但是你不用担心
BECAUSE I'M POSITIVE IT'S HER. I MEAN,WHO ELSE COULD IT BE? YEAH.
因为我肯定就是她，还能有谁
KARL'S OFFICE IS ALL GUYS, AND THEN THE ONLY WOMEN HE SEES
Karl办公的地方都是男人 他能接触的女人
ARE ME,JULIE,
只有，我，Julie
THAT-THAT LESBIAN THAT DOES HIS TAXES AND YOU.
那个收他税的女同志 还有你
YOU KNOW WHAT?
你知道我怎么想？
IT IS HER.
就是她
REALLY? WHY?
真的？为什么？
SHE JUST... SPIT IN YOUR WINGS.
她...她刚刚朝你身边吐口水
YOU GOT MY BACK?
你看得见我后面吗？
UH... SURE?
嗯...是的
HERE YOU GO,EXTRA SPICY.
来了，重辣来了
YOU DID THAT ON PURPOSE.
你故意的
YOU ARE GOING TO PAY!
你要付出代价的
FIGHT,FIGHT!
打，打
GET OFF ME,YOU! GET OFF ME!
你放开我 放开我
MAYER! FOUR ON ONE!
Mayer，她们四个打我一个
A LITTLE HELP!
我来帮你一下下
SO,UH,WHEN WE LEAVE...
我们要走的时候...
WHO YOU GONNA MISS THE MOST?
你会最想谁？
I DON'T KNOW.
我不知道
YEAH,YOU.
你当然知道
YOU SAID GOOD-BYE TO HER YET?
你和她告别过了吗？
NO.
没有
LO,MAN,IT'S... IT'S OKAY IF YOU LIKE HER.
听着，你可以喜欢她
YOU KNOW,I THINK DANIELLE REALLY LIKES YOU,TOO.
我觉得丹尼埃尔也喜欢你
REALLY?
真的？
YEAH,SHE TOLD ME SHE'D BE REALLY SAD
嗯，她告诉我，如果你不辞而别的话
IF YOU LEFT AND DIDN'T SAY GOOD-BYE.
她会很难过的
YOU KNOW,I THINK THAT
我觉得
SHE MIGHT EVEN WANT YOU TO GIVE HER A LITTLE KISS.
她可能还想让你轻吻她一下
BUT DANIELLE DOESN'T EVEN LIKE ME IN HER ROOM.
但是我在她房间里的时候 她都不喜欢我
SHE GETS MAD.
她特别生气
YEAH.
嗯
I TALKED TO HER ABOUT THAT. SHE FEELS REALLY BAD.
我和她聊过了 她感觉很抱歉
IF YOU COME IN HER ROOM AGAIN, SHE WON'T GET MAD.
如果你再去，她不会生气了
AND,CALEB,
Caleb
SHE'S GONNA ACT LIKE SHE DOESN'T WANT YOU TO KISS HER...
她可能会让你觉得 她不想让你吻她
BUT SHE DOES.
其实她想
DALE HELM,
Dale Helm
LIKE ALL THE STUDENTS AT PARSONS CHRISTIAN ACADEMY,
和所有在帕尔森教会学校的学生一样
WAS TAUGHT THAT HIS FUTURE WAS SAFELY IN GOD'S HANDS.
都被灌输这样的思想 你的未来尽由上帝掌握
WHAT HE DIDN'T KNOW
但他不知道的是
WAS THAT GABRIELLE SOLIS WAS ABOUT TO FORCE A FUMBLE.
Gabrielle Solis就快要 逼着他自己摸索未来了
ALL RIGHT,GUYS,
大家注意了
YOU ALL KNOW NEXT WEEK WE'RE PLAYING THE FALCONS!
你们都知道下个星期 我们就要和猎鹰队比赛了
AND WE'RE GONNA FRY UP THOSE BIRDIES FOR DINNER,
我们要把那些小鹰们炸了当晚饭
'CAUSE WE'RE THE HUSKIES!
因为我们是爱斯基摩队！
AND WHO ARE THE HUSKIES?
爱斯基摩队怎么样？
GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM!
上帝的球队！上帝的球队！
GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM!
GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM!
上帝的球队！上帝的球队
GOD'S TEAM! GOD'S TEAM!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? YOU CAN'T BE HERE.
你在这里干嘛？你怎么能在这里？
LET'S TALK TURKEY.
废话少说
WHAT IS IT GONNA TAKE FOR YOU TO GIVE UP THE BABY?
要怎么样你才放弃抚养权？
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN,OKAY? I GOTTA GET BACK.
那是不可能的 我要回去了
I'M THE QUARTERBACK. IT DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT.
我是四分位 这样不对
OKAY,NO,NO! WAIT,WHAT ABOUT A CAR?
等等，一辆车怎么样？
OR COLLEGE? TUITION'S A KILLER THESE DAYS.
或者大学 现在的学费贵得要死
I COULD HELP YOU OUT.
我可以帮你付
I DON'T NEED HELP.
我不需要你帮
YOU HEAR THOSE CHEERS? THOSE ARE FOR ME.
听到那些欢呼了？ 那都是给我的
LAST GAME, I THREW 246 YARDS.
上次比赛我扔出246码远
WITH STATS LIKE THAT,I CAN GET INTO THE COLLEGE OF MY CHOICE.
有这样的成绩 进哪所大学随便我挑
SO WHY DO YOU WANT TO BE A DAD?
那你为什么还想当爸爸？
THESE ARE YOUR GLORY DAYS. A BABY WOULD RUIN YOUR LIFE.
你正当年呢 要个孩子会毁了你生活
OH,I KNOW. BUT FRANK SAID ONCE I GET THE BABY, HE'S GONNA TAKE IT OFF MY HANDS.
我知道，但是Frank说 只要我一拿回抚养权，他就会接手
BUT IT'S NOT EVEN HIS. LIBBY DUMPED HIM.
这又不是他的孩子 Libby早把他甩了
HE THINKS THAT IF HE HAS THE BABY
他觉得，如果他得到孩子
AND SHE SEES HIM ACTING ALL MATURE,
她会觉得他成熟起来了
SHE'LL TAKE HIM BACK. NO,NO,NO.
然后会回到他身边的 不，不，不
I AM NOT LETTING THAT IDIOT USE MY BABY AS A BARGAINING CHIP.
我绝对不会让他个白痴 把我的孩子当砝码的
HEY,IT'S OUT OF MY HANDS!
喂，我又管不了这么多
NO,IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE,OKAY? JUST DO THE RIGHT THING
不是这样的 你要做该做的事
AND SIGN THE RELEASE FORM. LOOK,I'M REALLY SORRY.
签了这张放弃抚养权的表吧 听着，我真得很抱歉
BEFORE WE ADJOURN TODAY,
在启程前
LET'S TAKE A MENT TO BOW OUR HEADS.
我们还是做一下祷告吧
HELLO,EVERYONE.
大家好
I'M GABY SOLIS, CLASS OF '94. WHOO-HOO!
我是Gabi Solis 94届学生
I JUST WANTED TO GIVE GOD A BIG SHOUT OUT
我想大声歌颂上帝
FOR THIS AMAZING SEASON.
给我们如此精彩的一季比赛
THE MAN UPSTAIRS HAS DEFINITELY BEEN ON YOUR SIDE.
上帝一定同你们站在一起
AND YOU WANNA KNOW WHY? BECAUSE YOU BOYS LIVE CLEAN.
知道为什么吗？ 因为你们的生活很纯洁
YOU KEEP YOUR NOSES UP, YOU STAY OUT OF TROUBLE,
你们小心谨慎，你们远离麻烦
AND YOU DON'T GO AROUND GETTING STRIPPERS PREGNANT.
不会和脱衣舞娘胡闹，让她们怀孕
AND THAT'S A GOOD THING,
这很好
'CAUSE IF ONE OF YOU CAUSED A SCANDAL LIKE THAT,
因为如果你们中间的一个 出了这样的丑事
NOT ONLY WOULD THAT GUY GET KICKED OFF THE TEAM
不但会被踢出球队
AND LOSE ALL OF HIS SCHOLARSHIPS,
丢了所有奖学金
BUT GOD WOULD DROP YOUR SCHOOL COLORS SO FAST,
而且上帝也会很快遗弃你
IT'D MAKE YOUR HEAD SPIN!
会让你极为头疼
AND THEN THE FOOTBALL SEASON WOULD GO TO HELL.
那样的话，足球赛就见鬼去吧
NO PUN INTENDED.
就事论事，没有指桑骂槐
SO MY POINT IS,
我想说的是
DO THE RIGHT THING, AND NO ONE GETS HURT.
把事情做对了，没人会受伤害
SIGNED,SEALED,DELIVERED.
签了名，盖了章，都通过了
LILY'S OURS.
Lily是我们的了
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK? ARE YOU STAYING LATE AGAIN,
怎么样？ 你还要加班
OR CAN I FINALLY HAVE DINNER AT HOME WITH MY WIFE?
还是我终于可以和老婆一起在家晚餐了？
GOD,I DON'T KNOW. I'M GONNA GO CHECK WITH ED.
天哪，我也不知道 我去问问Ed
OKAY.
好
HEY,ANY LUCK WITH THAT I.M.ing THING?
嘿，短信有效果吗？
NO,NOT REALLY.
没有
I WAS ONLINE CHATTING WITH FRAN A WHILE AGO,
我刚才和Fran网上聊了一会儿
AND I ASKED HER WHAT SHE WAS WEARING,
我问她穿了什么
AND SHE SAID, "A YELLOW BLOUSE."
她说：“黄色的裙子”
OKAY,THAT'S GOOD. THEN WHAT?
挺好的阿 然后呢？
THEN... YEAH,THAT'S IT. I JUST KINDA BLOCKED.
然后...就这些 我就卡住了，不知道说什么
YOU BLOCKED?
- 你卡住了？
YEAH,I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO SAY.
恩，我不知道还能说些什么？
YOU'RE AN AWARD-WINNING COPYWRITER,ED.
Ed,你可是个得过奖的广告文案呀！
YOU GET PAID TO WRITE.
别人付钱买你的文章
YEAH,JINGLES FOR OATMEAL, NOT SOFT-CORE PORN.
那是麦片公司付的钱，又不是色情杂志
FOR GOD'S SAKES, IT'S NOT BRAIN SURGERY.
我的天 又不是让你做大脑手术
IS SHE STILL ONLINE?
- 她还在线吗？
YEAH,I THINK SO.
应该在的
"I LOVE THE WAY THAT BLOUSE CLINGS TO YOUR BODY."
“我喜欢那裙子紧紧裹着你身体的样子”
ARE YOU JOKING?
你开玩笑吗？
"ARE YOU JOKING?"
“你开玩笑吗？”
"NOTHING FUNNY ABOUT THOSE BEAUTIFUL BREASTS."
“谁会拿你迷人的胸部开玩笑”
"YEAH? WHAT DID YOU WANT TO DO TO ME?"
“真的？那你想做什么？”
ED,YOUR CONFERENCE CALL'S READY.
Ed,可以开会了
OH,GOD,I ALMT FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
天哪，我差点把这事忘了
OKAY, I GOTTA GO TAKE THIS,
我要去开会了
BUT YOU KEEP GOING, 'CAUSE YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
你继续，干得很好
NO,ED,I'M NOT DOING THIS FOR YOU!
不行Ed，我不能帮你干这种事
JUST... WHAT?
你就... 干什么？
"TOUCH EVERY INCH OF YOUR BODY
“抚摸你每一寸肌肤
UNTIL YOU'RE TREMBLING."
直到你发颤”
will u do that thing with ur teeth?
“用你的牙齿？”
"OH,YEAH. I'LL BITE YOU GOOD."
“嗯，我会咬得你很舒服的”
can i do that thing i did on the honeymoon?
我能干蜜月的时候做过的那件事吗？
"HELL,YEAH.
“当然”
FIRST,I WANT YOU TO TOUCH YOURSELF."
开始，我想你自己抚摸自己
r u?
你这样想？
"OH,YEAH!"
“当然”
Get home now!!!
现在就回来！
"I'M ON MY WAY."
我已经在路上了
HELLO?
喂？
Bree,it's Peter...
Bree，我是Peter
and I'm in trouble.
我有麻烦了
HI,I'M-I'M LOOKING FOR, UM,PETER McMILLAN.
你好，我是来，是来... 找Peter McMillon的
I'M NOT SURE I KNOW HIM.
我不知道认不认识他
YOU SHOULD ASK MY WIFE. SHE ORGANIZED THE PARTY.
你问问我老婆吧 是她办的聚会
HEY,JUDY,GET OVER HERE AND ACT LIKE A HOSTESS!
喂，Judie，过来，有点女主人的样子
COME ON IN! COME ON,COME ON,COME ON.
进来吧！ 进来呀，快进来，进来
HEY THERE.
你好
THINGS AREUST GETTING STARTED.
派对刚刚开始
AFTER YOU TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES, FEEL FREE TO JUMP RIGHT IN.
脱了衣服后,尽情娱乐
NO,NO,I'M-I'M GOOD.
不用了,我很好
I'M JUST,UM,HERE TO PICK UP MY FRIEND PETER.
我来接peter的
HE'S LOCKED HIMSELF IN YOUR BATHROOM,
他把自己锁在洗手间了
AND I'M HERE TO TAKE HIM HOME.
我是来带他回家的
OH,YEAH,THAT GUY WE WERE WONDERING ABOUT HIM.
是那个人啊 我们还在好奇呢
THE BATHROOM'S OVER THERE.
洗手间在那里
HEY,IS THAT YOUR NATURAL COLOR?
嘿,你没染发吧
YES,IT IS.
是啊
BEAUTIFUL. I WISH MINE WOULD DO THAT.
真美 我也想和你的一样
THIS IS OUT OF A BOTTLE.
糟糕的头发
YES,I'M AWARE OF THAT.
是的,我看出来了
PETER?
PETER,IT'S BREE. ARE YOU IN THERE?
PETER,是BREE 你在吗?
WHATRE YOU DOING HERE?
你干什么呢?
I'M A S
我是性瘾者 你说呢?
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY BE TURNED ON BY WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE.
你不会因为外面的派对而性奋吧
DISGUSTING,ISN'T IT? YES. WHY WOULD YOU WANNA COME TO A PLACE LIKE THIS?
很恶心,是吧? 你为什么要来?
I DIDN'T. I WANTED YOU TO COME.
不是的 我想让你来
I CAN'T MAKE YOU NOT HAVE FEELINGS FOR ME,
我不能阻止你喜欢我
BUT I CAN SHOW YOU WHO I WAS, WHAT MY LIFE WAS LIKE.
但我可以让你看到真正的我
WELL,THAT'S NOT YOUR LIFE ANYMORE.
这不是你的生活
BUT IT COULD BE.
但可能是
IF I SLIP AGAIN,THIS IS EXACTLY WHERE YOU COULD FIND ME,
如果我失守,这里就是我来的地方
OR SEPLACE WORSE.
或更糟的地方
THEN WHAT WOULD YOU THINK OF ME?
到时你会怎么看我?
PETER- BREE...
IT'S DANGEROUSTO CARE
关心我是危险的
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE OVER THE YEARS,
这些年不少人帮我
AND THEY ALL END UP GETTING HURT.
但都以失败告终
REX SAID HE'D ALWAYS BE FAITHFUL.
REX说他忠心不二
GEORGE SAID HE'D NEVER HURT ME.
GEORGE他永远不会伤害我
AND AS IT TURNED OUT, THEY WERE BOTH LIARS.
最后发现,他们都在说谎
SO AS LONG AS YOU'RE HONEST WITH ME,
只要你对我诚实
YOU'D BE AMAZED AT WHAT I CAN PUT UP WITH.
我就能忍受一切
NOW LET'S GO HOME.
回家吧
HEY THERE. DID YOU HAVE A LATE NIGHT?
嘿,你熬夜了?
I HOPE.
我希望是
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
太恐怖了
THE WHOLE THING BLEW UP IN MY FACE.
事情搞砸了
WHY ULD YOU TELL MY WIFE TO BITE MY NIPPLE OFF?
你为什么对我老婆说要咬我的乳头?
I DIDN'T!
我没说!
I DIDN'T. WHY WOULD SHE-OH!
我没说! 为什么她要 哦!
THE HONEYMOON THING.
蜜月
YEAH,AND IT HURT LIKE HELL THEN,TOO.
真是痛不欲生
AND IT DIDN'T TAKE HER LONG TO FIGURE OUT
她立即就发现
THAT I LET A STRANGER SEDUCE HER ONLINE.
我让陌生人去勾引她
OH,GOD!
天哪!
SHE WAS SO MAD,SHE LOCKED HERSELF IN THE BATHROOM
她气极了,把自己锁在了洗手间
AND CALLED A DIVORCE LAWYER.
打电话给律师,要求离婚
YOU'RE GETTING DIVORCED?
你们要离婚?
I SPENT TWO HOURS PLEADING WITH HER THROUGH THE BATHROOM DOOR,
我花了2个小时在门前哀求
BEGGING HER NOT TO LEAVE ME,AND...
求她不要离开我
WE FINALLY MANAGED TO COME TO TERMS.
最后我们达成了协议
WHAT KIND OF TERMS?
- 什么样的协议?
I PROMISED HER WOULD FIRE THE PERSON WHO DID IT.
我对她保证,我解雇和她聊天的人
YOU'RE GONNA FIRME?
你要解雇我?
NO,OF COURSE NOT. YOU'RE TOO IMPORTANT HERE.
当然不了 你是重要人物
I'M GONNA FIRE TOM.
我要解雇TOM
I TOLD HER IT WAS HIM THAT SENT THE I.M.s.
我告诉她是tom干的
WHAT?! I TOLD HER THAT HE HAD A PROBLEM WITH BOUNDARIE
什么 我告诉她tom不知好歹
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T WANNA DO THIS,
我抱歉,我也不想
BUT MY MARRIAGE WAS ON THE LINE.
但我的婚姻岌岌可危
YOU CAN'T MAKE MY HUSBAND YOUR SCAPEGOAT.
你不能拿我丈夫当替罪羊
I WON'T LET YOU.
我不会同意的
I DON'T HAVE A DAMN CHOICE.
我没的选择
I CAN'T BE DIVORCED, LYNETTE.
我不能离婚 LYNETTE.
I CAN'T.
不能
HE'S UNDER CONTRACT.
他还有合约
IF YOU JUST FIRE HIM,
如果你解雇他
HE'LL SUE YOU,AND I'LL BACK HIM UP. YOU NEED CAUSE.
我会支持他告你 你要找理由
WELL...
那么
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO FIND CAUSE.
我想需要理由
IT SHOULDN'T BE TOO DIFFICULT IF I LOOK HARD ENOUGH.
仔细找能发现
HEY,HOW'S THE EYE?
嘿,眼睛好点了吗?
OH,IT'S STILL A LITTLE RED,
有点红
BUl THINK I GOT ALL THE HOT SAUCE OUT.
但我把所有辣酱都弄出来了
THAT'S GOOD.
那就好
SO,UM... YOU KNOW THE OTHER DAY
那天
WHEN I SAID THAT THING ABOUT US BEING SISTERS?
我说我们要做好姐妹?
WELL,WHEN I SAID IT I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN IT.
我不是故意的
YEAH, I KIND OF FIGURED THAT.
我了解
NO,I MEAN,I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN IT. BUT,UM...
我是说我真的不是故意的
NOW I DO.
现在我是真心的了
THANK YOU. THANK YOU FOR HAVING MY BACK.
谢谢你支持我
SO DO I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT YOU ATTACKING ANY MORE WAITRESSES?
你还会去攻击女招待吗?
NAH, MYAR BRAWLIN' DAYS ARE OVER.
我洗手不干了
OH,YOU KNOW,I-I'VE GOTTA GO. I HAVE A MEETING.
我要走了,我要开会
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
再谈
ARE YOU OLIVER?
你是OLIVER?
YOU MUST BE EDIE. PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
你一定是EDIE 很高兴见到你
OH,LIKEWISE.
一样一样
I HEAR YOU'RE ONE OF THE BEST PRIVATE DETECTIVES IN TOWN.
我听说你是这里最好的私家侦探
I DO WHAT I CAN.
夸奖
WELL,COME ON IN. LET'S TALK.
进去说
UM... BASICALLY,I JUST WANT YOU TO TRAIL MY EX.
我要追踪前男朋友
HE,UH... LEFT ME FOR ANOTHER WOMAN,
他为别的女人甩了我
AND I WANNA NAIL THAT HO TO THE WALL.
我要查出是哪个贱人
CALEB?
HEY,COME ON,BUDDY, WAKE UP.
快,起来了
CALEB?
IT'S TIME.
是时候了
GET AWAY FROM ME!
离我远点!
GET AWAY FROM HER!
离她远点!
DANIELLE,I WANT YOU TO PICK UP THE PHONE AND CALL THE POLICE.
DANIELLE,你去报警
NO! WHAT?
不! 为什么?
MATTHEW AND HIS MOTHER HAVE BEEN PROTECTING CALEB.
MATTHEW和他妈妈一直在保护CALEB
THEY'RE IN AS MUCH TROUBLE AS HE IS!
他们一家麻烦已经够多
I DON'T CARE.
我不管
MOM,PLEASE! I LOVE HIM.
妈妈,求你了,我爱他
PLEASE.
求你了
IF I HADN'T BEEN IN THE HOUSE,
如果我不在房间里
HEOULD'VE RAPED HER... OR WORSE.
他会强奸了她 或更糟
HE'S LOCKED IN HIS ROOM NOW,SO...
他被锁去房间了
NEEDLESS TO SAY, THE AGREEMENT BETWEEN US IS OFF.
我们的约定已经无效
CALEB IS DANGEROUS, AND I WANT HIM PUT AWAY.
CALEB是危险人物 我要他进精神病院
IF HE IS NOT GONE BY TOMORROW, I AM CALLING THE POLICE.
如果他明天不走,我就报警
HE WILL BE. I PROMISE YOU.
他会走的,我保证
CAN I GO CHECK ON DANIELLE?
我能去看看DANIELLE吗?
YES.
可以
BETTY,I AM SERIOUS.
BETTY,我很认真
EITHER YOU DO SOMETHING, OR I WILL.
我们间总要有人行动
EE,STOP WORRYING.
bree,不用担心
I UNDERSTAND WHAT NEEDS TO HAPPEN NOW.
我知道现在要做什么
DANIELLE?
DID IT WORK?
奏效了?
PERFECTLY.
当然
YOU DID GREAT.
你做的好
UM,SO I GOT SOME RATES ON SOME MENTAL HOSPITALS AROUND HERE,
我有精神康复院的排名
AND THERE'S ONE CALLED SILVERCREST
有一家叫SILVERCREST
WHICH ACTUALLY SEEMS OKAY.
看来不错
PUT THIS HAM IN THE FRIDGE, WILL YOU?
把火腿把进冰箱
I THINK I'LL MAKE IT FOR DINNER.
我要用来做晚餐
UH,MOM,I KNOW YOU DON'T WANNA TALK ABOUT THIS,BUT WE HAVE TO.
妈,我知道你不想谈,但我们不得不说
MRS. VAN DE KAMP IS GONNA CALL THE POLICE.
VAN DE KAMP太太会报警的
I PROMISED MYSELF I WOULD NEVER INSTITUTIONALIZE YOUR OTHER.
我发过誓 绝对不会把你哥哥送进精神康复院的
MOM... HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT'D BE BEFORE HE'D ACT OUT,
妈... 你觉得离他下次发作前还有多久
MAYBE EVEN HURT SOMEBODY?
他也许还会伤人
A COUPLE OF DAYS? A WEEK?
几天？一个星期？
THEN THEY'D THROW HIM IN A STRAITJACKET
然后他们就给他套上病服
AND DRUG AWAY WHAT'S LEFT OF HIS MIND.
夺走他仅有的一点理智
HE'D SPEND THE REST OF HIS LIFE AT THE MERCY OF STRANGERS.
他的下半生就要听凭别人摆布
BUT IF WE DON'T SEND HIM TO A HOSPITAL,
但是如果我们不送他去医院
HE'S GONNA END UP IN PRISON,
他就要进监狱了
AND DON'T YOU THINK THAT'S WORSE?
你觉得那样会更遭吗？
YES,OF COURSE I DO.
当然
SO WHAT THE HELL ARE WE GONNA DO?
那么我们该怎么办？
PHENOBARBITAL?
安眠药？
IT'S EASY.
很简单
IT'S PAINLESS.
没有痛苦
IT'S JUST A FEW EXTRA DROPS. HE SIMPLY FALLS ASLEEP.
多滴几滴，他就会睡过去的
CALEB WAS MEANT FOR A BETTER WORLD THAN THIS,MATTHEW.
MATTHEW， CALBE应该去一个更好的世界
IT'S TIME TO GIVE YOUR BROTHER THE PEACE HE DESERVES.
是时候给你哥哥他应得的安宁了
WHO'S THE PRETTY GIRL?
哪个小姑娘这么漂亮啊？
OH,LOOKS LIKE IT'S DADDY'S TURN.
呵呵，看来该让爸爸抱了
I GOT HER. YES.
好
OH,YES.
好了
MRS. SOLIS?
SOLIS夫人？
YES?
什么事？
WE HAVE A COURT ORDER TO TAKE THE COLLINS BABY INTO CUSTODY.
根据法院裁决 我们要看护collins夫妇的孩子
NO,NO,NO, THAT'S A MISTAKE.
不可能，肯定弄错了
NO,WE- WE HAVE THE PAPERWORK.
不对，我们有文件
THE BIRTH FATHER SIGNED AWAY HIS RIGHTS.
孩子的生父放弃了抚养权
IT'S THE BIRTH MOTHER WHO'S PROTESTING.
是她的生母提出的上诉
WHAT?
什么？
UNTIL THE ADOPTION IS LEGALLY FINALIZED,
直到收养的法律手续正是办完以前
THE BIRTH MOTHER CAN STILL CHANGE HER MIND,
生母都可以改变主意
AND... SHE HAS.
她...她变卦了
NO,NO, NO,NO,NO,NO!
不，不，不！
GABY,WAIT.
GABY，等等
YOU? YOU DON'T EVEN WANNA BE A MOTHER!
你？你都不想做妈妈
WELL,LOOK,FRANK QUIT USIN',ANDUH,
FRANK戒掉了，而且...
HE GOT A GOOD JOB DOWN AT THE PLANT. HE'S REALLY STEPPED UP.
他在工厂找了份好工作 他改了很多
SO?!
所以，你们？！
WELL,SO WE'RE GONNA GIVE THE WHOLE FAMILY THING A SHOT.
所以，我们想试试组成个家
WELL,I'LL TOTALLY GIVE YOU ALL YOUR MONEY BACK.
我会把所有的钱都还给你的
I DON'T WANT MY MONEY BACK. I WANT MY BABY!
我不要钱,我要我的宝宝
CO ON,LET'S GO.
来吧,我们走
CARLOS!
Carlos！
NO! CARLOS,WHAT'S HAPPENING?
不,Carlos,发生什么事?
NO,NO,NO,MA'AM, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
不不不,警官 你不明白
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, THIS IS OUR BABY!
你不明白,这是我们的小孩!
NO,WE'VE BEEN-WE'VE BEEN FEEDING HER,AND WE-
不,我们一直在喂她奶,还有-
WE'VE BEEN BATHING HER,
我们给她洗澡
AND WE WAKE UP IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT AND WE ROCK HER,
我们还半夜起床摇哄她
WHICH IS CRAZY,
这样做很疯狂
'CAUSE IF YOU KNEW ME, I DON'T DO THAT.
如果你了解我们的话 就知道那不是我们的风格
I DON'T DO THAT.
我一向不那样的
AND-AND MY HUSBAND- MY HUSBAND,HE SINGS TO HER.
还有还有我丈夫,他还给她唱歌
HE SINGS, SO YOU CAN'T TAKE HER AWAY.
他唱歌 所以你不能把她带走！
IT'S TOO LATE. WE'VE ALREADY FALLEN IN LOVE WITH HER!
太迟了，我们已经爱上她了
CARLOS,DO SOMETHING!
Carlos，做点什么！
NO,YOU CAN'T GO! YOU CAN'T-YOU CAN'T TAKE HER!
不，你不能走，你不能把她带走！
YOU CAN'T TAKE HER!
你不能把她带走！
NO!
不！
SHE'S OUR BABY!
她是我们的宝宝！
SHE'S OUR...
她是我们的...
NO!
不！
PLEASE!
求你了！
THERE IS A PRAYER INTENDED TO GIVE STRENGTH TO PEOPLE
祷文意图要赐给人们力量
FACED WITH CIRCUMSTANCES THEY DON'T WANT TO ACCEPT.
当面对他们不想接受的情况的时候
THE POWER OF THE PRAYER
祷文的力量
COMES FROM ITS INSIGHT INTO HUMAN NATURE...
来自它对人类本性的深刻洞察力
WE ASK GOD TO GRANT US THE SERENITY
我们企求上帝给我们安详的勇气
TO ACCEPT THE THINGS WE CANNOT CHANGE...
去接受我们不能改变的东西
BECAUSE SO MANY OF US
因为我们中很多人
RAGE AGAINST THE HAND THAT LIFE HAS DEALT US...
对与我们做对的命运之手惟有愤怒
THE COURAGE TO CHANGE THE THINGS WE CAN...
还有改变我们能改变的东西的勇气
BECAUSE SO MANY OF US ARE COWARDLY
因为我们很多人懦夫一般的
D AFRAID TO STAND UP FOR WHAT IS RIGHT...
没有勇气为正义拍案而起
AND THE WISDOM TO KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
还有辨别事实的睿智
BECAUSE SO MANY OF US GIVE IN TO DESPAIR...
因为我们中很多人对绝望妥协
WHEN FACED WITH AN IMPOSSIBLE CHOICE.
当面对一个不可能的选择的时候
THE GOOD NEWS FOR THOSE WHO UTTER THESE WORDS
好消息是 对那些把那些话说出口的人
IS THAT GOD WILL HEAR YOU AND ANSWER YOUR PRAYER.
那就是上帝会听到你的祈祷并给你答复
THE BAD NEWS IS THAT SOMETIMES THE ANSWER IS NO. The Desperate Housewives Season 02  Episode 20
但坏消息是 有的时候答案可能是否定的 绝望的主妇 第2季 第20集
The End-
=完=-